{
    "id": "7245f1b6574a428b993a269a3ad9ae0f",
    "title": "Determiners Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "They worked hard although there was ……………………….. chance of success.",
            "description": "Little is similar to no.",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "a little",
                "the little"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. money we had helped us immensely.",
            "description": "The little means not much but all that there is.",
            "answers": [
                "Little",
                "A little",
                "The little"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "There is …………………………. food in the fridge if you are hungry.",
            "description": "A little means some or not much. It has a positive meaning.",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "a little",
                "the little"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… foreigners can write perfect English.",
            "description": "Few means hardly any. It has a negative meaning.",
            "answers": [
                "Few",
                "A few",
                "The few"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I would like to ask ………………………… questions.",
            "description": "A few means some.",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "a few",
                "the few"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. libraries that we have are not properly maintained.",
            "description": "The few means not many but all that there is.",
            "answers": [
                "Few",
                "A few",
                "The few"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "We did not get …………………………. help.",
            "description": "Any is used in negatives and interrogatives. ",
            "answers": [
                "any",
                "some",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "There is …………………………. water in the bottle if you are thirsty.",
            "description": "Some is used in affirmative sentences. ",
            "answers": [
                "some",
                "any"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Will you give me …………………………… to eat?",
            "description": "Some is used in interrogative sentences, when we expect an affirmative answer.",
            "answers": [
                "anything",
                "something"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven’t heard ………………………….. from them.",
            "description": "Anything is used in negatives.",
            "answers": [
                "anything",
                "something"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………… politicians are really honest.",
            "description": "We use few with plural nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "Few",
                "Little",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": ".............................. money was wasted on the project.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Much",
                "Most"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}